Bhaiya fulfill the bond of my Rakhi, come on,
stand up, you are sleeping even on Rakhi day
[screaming sound] stand up quickly, I have to tie the Rakhi, I am
standing, let me
sleep, friend, I have got a holiday today, let me sleep,
stand up, friend, I have to go with my aunt,
then I have to go to play, stand up
quickly, get the Rakhi made, see how nice I am, take it and
tie it, stand up,
Mummy did not teach us to get the
Rakhi made while sitting,
friend,
take it,
tie it and cover your head.
Take it and cover it.
I want to get my photo taken in it.  Don't you have to stand up?
Cover your head, I have
covered my head.
Take
a second.   You have
brought a gift for me, right?   Are
?  What kind of gift?
Hey, this time I have brought sweets for you from my pocket.
This time he will give me a gift.
I told you.
You can eat this sweet also.  You can also tie the Rakhi.  You will
not get any gift.   Even with
such a low salary, he still wants a gift.
What kind of a person is my neighbor Chintu, I will get him tied up.  You
give me ₹100 but you do
n't give me anything.
Go and get it tied.  He even beats you.
You you you don't kill.  Won't you kill
me?  I can't even give a gift.  I'm a
dog bastard, my brother is dead.
How are you giving the pill?
died.
How to shoot?
Not Rakhi [laughs] Mar.
Yes, she will abuse me on Rakhi day.
How are you killing me?   Take it.   You have
ruined my [screaming] hair, my entire makeup, my entire makeup,
my entire makeup [screaming] you
will die on Rakhi day, you are dead, I will
not tie a Rakhi to you, I will not tie a Rakhi to you
[screaming] [
groaning]
Anuj
[music]
[laughter]
you also feed me.
[Laughter]